Eloise Hubbard Linscott collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series II: Sound Recordings
  - SR429, October 30-31, 1957, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, double-track, mono.; 7 in.
    - Side A: Chanteys, afc1942002_sr429a
  - SR430, October 30-31, 1957, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, mono.; 7 in.
    - Side A: Signing Articles, afc1942002_sr430a
  - SR431, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7.5 ips, mono.; 7 in.
    Selections from recordings of William J. (Jack) Sherrard.
    - Side A: Tape Recording Selections from William J. Sherrard, afc1942002_sr431a
      - Sherrard sings chantey with explanations
      - Sherrard sings Rio Grande with few explanations of working a ship
      - Sherrard sings chanteys
      - Selections from chantey album "Songs of the Squareriggers" - script, sound effects, chanteyman and crew.
  - SR432, November 16, 1965, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3.75 ips, mono.; 7 in.
    - Side A: Phrases from the Sea and/or Terms of Deep Water Life, afc1942002_sr432a
  - SR433
    - Side A: The Jackie Gleason Show, December 8 and 15, 1962, 1 sound tape reel: analog, mono.; 7 in.; afc1942002_sr433a
      The songs are preceded by and interspersed with comedy sketches. Frank Fontaine sings "When Your Hair Has Turned to Silver," which Linscott incorrectly identifies as "Always."
      - When Your Hair Has Turned to Silver
      - I'm Dreaming of a White Christmas [White Christmas]
      - Auld Acquaintance [Auld Lang Syne]
  - SR434, undated, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips, double-track, mono.; 7 in.
    Performed by the Bourne Male Quartet and Chorus and William J. (Jack) Sherrard
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr434a
      - Johnny's Gone to Hilo
      - Ryo Grande [1]
      - Leave Her, Johnny, Leave Her
      - Ryo Grande [2]
      - Blow the Man Down
      - Explanation of phrases "pigs in your boots," "Jacob's ladder," "monkey's fist," and "bitter end"
      - A Long Time Ago
  - SR435, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips, mono.; 5 in.
    Performed by Charles (Uncle Charlie) Ronco, in Dover-Foxcroft, Maine. Songs in French and English. Duplicated from Linscott's original disc recordings (1943-1946) by Peter Fagley, on January 20, 1974.
    - Side A: Lumberjack songs, tape 2, afc1942002_sr435a
      - Rossignol Sauvage
      - Sparrow
      - Late Evening Dew
      - Prince Edward Island Song
      - Bachelor Song
      - Emma Jean
      - French Wedding Song
  - SR436, circa 1950s, 1 sound tape reel: analog, mono.; 5 in.
    Charles Linscott (son of John and Ardes Linscott) is the baby heard in track 1.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr436a
      - Baby's Cry
      - Bunco Kelly
      - Ele lecture [Lecture given by Eloise Hubbard Linscott]
      - Sherrard-Paddy Get Back [Paddy Get Back]
      - Western Ocean
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr436b
      - II Dreadnaught
      - Western Ocean
      - B Kelly start [Bunco Kelly]
  - SR437, undated, 1 sound tape reel: analog, mono.; 5 in.
    - Side A: Interview with Mr. and Mrs. Harold Stead, afc1942002_sr437a
  - SR438, undated, 1 sound tape reel: analog, mono.; 5 in.
    Dubs of commercial recordings for approximately the first half of the tape. Part of the tape is recorded at the wrong speed, followed by a section of what may be home recordings.
    - Side A: Charles Stead's records - music, afc1942002_sr438a
  - SR439, February 7, 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, mono.; 5 in.
    Performed by Edward A. (Ed) Lewis (fiddle) and Eloise Hubbard Linscott (piano). Recordings that follow this section seem to have been copied from a radio broadcast. At the very end of the recording is more fiddle music by Lewis.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr439a
      - Tuning
      - Haste to the Wedding [Come Haste to the Wedding]
      - Fisher's Hornpipe
      - Devil's Dream
      - Soldier's Joy
      - Chorus Jig
      - The Girl I Left Behind Me
      - Various audio clips of square dances
      - Unidentified fiddle tune (fragment)
  - SR440, October 20, 1957, 1 sound tape reel: analog, mono.; 5 in.
    The first two songs performed by performed by Jimmy Hathcock. The third song performed by L.E. Chrysler. The balance of the tape is recordings of Linscott, her son John, daughter-in-law Ardes, and grandson Charles.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr440a
      - Love Always Has Its Way
      - Boston Burglar
      - The Miller
      - Jingle Bells
      - The Witch Doctor
      - I've Been Working on the Railroad
      - “Grace”
  - SR441, 1962, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips, mono.; 5 in.
    Recording made by Eric Hillis of Halifax, Nova Scotia.
    - Side A: Voyage of MGM's Bounty: Vancouver to Boston, with Calls at Major Ports, afc1942002_sr441a
  - SR442, August 2 and 16, 1964, 1 sound tape reel: analog, mono.; 5 in.
    Performers include Alice Cyr (for songs 1 through 3), Gil Edgerly, Royall Prindle, and Eldridge Robie. Edgerly, Prindle, and Robie participated in the bull session).
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr442a
      - Teaching French in Killilou
      - Jolly Irishman
      - Clancy's Wooden Wife
      - Bull session of Old Times
  - SR443, August 23, 1964, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips, mono.; 5 in.
    Recordings made in Gene's Coffee Shop, East Wolfeboro, New Hampshire. Performers include the following: Dearborn, bass and electric guitar (Wolfeboro, New Hampshire); Les Dorr, guitar (Kittery, Maine); Lyle Glidden, guitar (East Wolfeboro, New Hampshire); Beaulieu A. MacIver, fiddle (Gonic, New Hampshire).
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr443a
  - SR444, circa December 1951, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, mono.; 5 in.
    Performers include the Cotton Mountain Boys, Horace Roberts, and Lyle Glidden. Recorded at Gene's coffee shop, East Wolfeboro, New Hampshire.
    - Side A: Cotton mountain Boys: Christmas 1951, afc1942002_sr444a
    - Side B: Lyle Glidden Side II, afc1942002_sr444b
  - SR445, circa December 1956-December 31, 1957, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, mono.; 5 in.
    "Frozen Logger" and "Kisses Sweeter Than Wine" performed by Jo Mapes (guitar and vocals); recorded from a television broadcast. "Fooling around on the tape" includes Linscott, John, Charles, and Bob Partridge having a conversation."McGilligan's Ball" performed by Arthur Godfrey and Carmel Quinn. Edward A. (Ed) Lewis performs "How I'd Like Someone to Love Me..." (his own composition) on fiddle. "Haste to the Wedding" and "Soldier's Joy" performed by Lews (fiddle) and Linscott (piano).
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr445a
      - Spoken introduction by Linscott
      - Frozen Logger
      - Fooling around on the tape
      - Kisses Sweeter Than Wine
      - McGilligan's Ball
      - Conversation between Godfrey and Carmel Quinn
      - How I'd Like to Have Someone to Love Me Like I Could Love Someone Like You
      - Haste to the Wedding [Come Haste to the Wedding]
      - Soldier's Joy
  - SR446, December 25, 1956; December 31, 1957, 1 sound tape reel: analog, mono.; 5 in.
    - Side A: Programs recorded from TV and LPs, afc1942002_sr446a
    - Side B: Programs recorded from TV and LPs, afc1942002_sr446b
  - SR447, November 1964, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips, mono.; 3 in.
    Performed by William J. (Jack) Sherrard and John Hubbard Linscott. Sherrard provides extensive explanations throughout. Recorded at 36 Mayo Avenue, Needham, Massachuseets (Linscott family home).
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr447a
      - Johnny's Gone to Hilo
      - Ryo Grande
  - SR448, November 18, 1965, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips, mono.; 3 in.
    Performed by William J. (Jack) Sherrard, Eloise Hubbard Linscott, and John Hubbard Linscott.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr448a
      - Jack Sherrard explaining sails that were used on a corsair
      - Time for Us to Leave Her
  - SR449, 1 audiocassette: analog, mono.
    Linscott and an unidentified man listen to and discuss a sound recording, and provide commentary as they listen. Some speed problems occur during the recording.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr449a
      - Under His Wing
      - Pass Me Not, O Gentle Savior
      - The Spanish Cavalier
      - Home! Sweet Home!
      - Lass of Mohea
      - Unidentified
      - Fair Fanny Moore
      - Sweet Genevieve
      - Just Before the Battle, Mother
      - The Convict and the Rose
      - Unidentified poem or lyrics
  - SR450, 1938 (unconfirmed), 1 wax cylinder: analog.
    Performed by Smith Paine (fiddle), in Wolfeboro, New Hampshire. Cylinder #1. Slate announced by Erika Brady.
    - Untitled, afc1942002_sr450
    - Chorus Jig
    - Maid in the Pump Room
    - Lady of the Lake
    - Come Haste to the Wedding
    - Sweet Ellen
    - Sicilian Circle
    - Music for the dance Virginia Reel:
      Contents:
      Irish Washerwoman
      White Cockade
      Yankee Doodle
  - SR451, July 1938, 1 wax cylinder: analog.
    Performed by Edson H. Cole (fiddle and calls), in Freedom, New Hampshire. Cylinder #2. Slate announced by Erika Brady.
    - Music for the dance Green Mountain Volunteers:, afc1942002_sr451
    - Irish Washerwoman [1]
    - Five-Step Schottische
    - Music for the dance Virginia Reel:
      Kinloch
      Irish Washerwoman [2]
      Sicilian Circle
      Larry O'Gaff
  - SR452, July 1938, 1 wax cylinder: analog.
    "Portland Fancy" and "Soldier's Joy") performed by Edson H. Cole (fiddle and calls), in Freedom, New Hampshire. All other tunes performed by Willie (Bill) Woodward (fiddle and calls), of Bristol New Hampshire. Cylinder #3. Slate announced by Erika Brady.
    - Portland Fancy, afc1942002_sr452
    - Soldier's Joy
    - Speed the Plough
    - Hull's Victory
    - Pop Goes the Weasel
    - Music for the dance Boston Fancy:
      Soldier's Hornpipe
      Old Zip Coon
  - SR453, circa 1938, 1 wax cylinder: analog.
    "Perrie, Merrie, Dixi, Domini " performed by Eloise Hubbard Linscott. All other selections performed by Smith Paine (fiddle), in Wolfeboro, New Hampshire. Cylinder #4. Slate announced by Erika Brady.
    - Perrie, Merrie, Dixi, Domini, afc1942002_sr453
    - Merry Dance
    - Pigtown Fling
    - Captain Keeler
    - Plain Jig
  - SR454, October 1938, 1 wax cylinder: analog.
    The untitled song and "Oxen Song" performed by Sam Young, of North Anson, Maine. All other songs performed by Fred Pullen, of North Anson, Maine. Cylinder #5. Slate announced by Erika Brady.
    - I Am a Rich Widow, afc1942002_sr454
    - Here Stands an Old Maid Forsaken
    - Green Grow the Rushes, Oh
    - On the Green Carpet
    - Oats, Peas, Beans and Barley
    - The Needle's Eye
    - Untitled
    - Oxen Song
  - SR455, September 1938, 1 wax cylinder: analog.
    Performed by Charles Young, of Moultonboro, New Hampshire. Cylinder #6. Slate announced by Erika Brady.
    - Oxen Song, afc1942002_sr455
    - Jack Haggerty
    - Old Woman in Dover
    - The Jam on Gerry's Rocks
    - The Lumberman's Alphabet
  - SR456, July 1938, 1 wax cylinder: analog.
    Performed by Edson H. Cole (fiddle and calls), in Freedom, New Hampshire. Cylinder #7. Slate announced by Erika Brady.
    - Lancier's Quadrille, afc1942002_sr456
    - Music for the dance Boston Fancy:
      Contenst:
      Turkey in the Straw
      The Tempest
  - SR457, July 1938, 1 wax cylinder: analog.
    Calls for "Plain Quadrille" and concertina played for "Mocking Bird" by Willie (Bill) Woodward, of Bristol, New Hampshire. A last, untitled selection is documented for this cylinder, and performed by Niles, Patricia, John, and Eloise, but nothing like it is audible is heard on the recording. Cylinder #8. Slate announced by Erika Brady.
    - Plain Quadrille, afc1942002_sr457
    - Mocking Bird
  - SR458, July 11, 1938, 1 wax cylinder: analog.
    Performed by Willie (Bill) Woodward (calls), of Bristol, New Hampshire. Cylinder #9. Slate announced by Erika Brady.
    - Ninepin Quadrille, afc1942002_sr458
    - Nellie Gray
    - Promenade for Double Virginia Reel:
      Irish Washerwoman [1]
  - SR459, undated, 1 wax cylinder: analog.
    Linscott performs all the songs (except "Rolling of the Stones"), and gives the names of performers/informants who originally provided the songs. After a long pause following "Billy Martin," and before "Rolling of the Stone," different people can be heard speaking or reciting in turn. An unidentified man performs “Rolling of the Stones.” The recording has speed problems. Cylinder #10. Slate announced by Erika Brady.
    - Whistling song, afc1942002_sr459
    - The Needle's Eye
    - Green Grow the Rushes, Oh
    - I Am a Rich Widow
    - Bold Dicky
    - Billy Martin
    - Fragments of recitations
    - Rolling of the Stones
    - Untitled
  - SR460, undated, 1 wax cylinder: analog.
    Performed by Sam Young, of North Anson, Maine. Cylinder #11. Slate announced by Erika Brady.
    - Oxen Song, afc1942002_sr460
    - Peter Emily [Peter Emberly; Prince Edward Island Song]
- Series III: Graphic Materials, 200 black-and-white photos, 30 film negatives
  Original and copy negatives are filed sequentially, by digital ID number. Since not all prints have matching negatives, there are gaps between numbers. The prints are filed alphabetically within “People A-Z,” and geographically in “Landscapes and Views.” The result is that the digital IDs reflect digital rather than sequential order. The digital IDs are given below, in the order in which they are housed in the boxes. In photos with multiple individuals, names given reflect left-to right identification of individuals depicted.
  - Subseries A: Photographic materials (phyiscal items)
    - Negatives, undated, 103 negatives; PH001-002, PH004-007, PH011-016, PH018-019, PH021-026, PH028, PH030-031, PH032-036, PH038-PH051, PH055-057, PH059-063, PH068-070, PH073, PH077-080, PH086-092, PH095-097, PH099-116, PH118-121, PH123-127, PH130-133, PH0135, PH137-140 (Box-folder 25)
    - Negatives, undated, 76 negatives; PH141-146, PH149-169, PH 171-188, PH190-194, PH197-212, PH214-215, PH217, PH220-226 (Box-folder 26)
    - Photographic prints removed from Folk Songs of Old New England (association copy), circa 1929-1940s, 21 prints; MS084_0006, MS085_0002, MS085_0018, MS085_0024, MS085_0052, MS086_0009, MS086_0017, MS086_0025, MS086_0037, MS086_0044, MS086_0063, MS086_0076, MS087_0003, MS087_0009, MS088_0024, MS088_0047, MS088_0074, MS088_0085, MS088_0098, MS088_0131, MS088_0171 (Box-folder 27/234)
      These photos were taped into Linscott’s copy of her book (in Box 14). In order to represent the digitized images in the original order among the book pages, it was necessary to assign each photo an “ms” number (to indicate a manuscript item), rather than a “ph” number (to indicate a photographic item). Most of the photos are similar to other photos in this collection, and these instances are noted below.
    - People, A-E, undated, 24 prints; PH001-011, PH014-015, PH017-025 (Box-folder 27/235)
      Includes photographic prints for PH001-028, excluding PH012-013, PH016, and PH026.
    - People, F-K, undated, 22 prints; PH029-PH032, PH034, PH036-047, PH049-054 (Box-folder 27/236)
      The variants for PH032, representing different versions of this photo, were not digitized.
    - People, L, undated, 19 prints; PH055-059, PH063-072, PH074-076, PH147 (Box-folder 27/237)
    - People, M-O, undated, 10 prints; PH077-086 (Box-folder 27/238)
    - People, P-R, undated, 24 prints; PH087-109, PH142 (Box-folder 27/239)
    - People, S, undated, 20 prints; PH110-129 (Box-folder 27/240)
    - People, T-Z, undated, 13 prints; PH130-139, PH141, PH146, PH151 (Box-folder 27/241)
    - Landscapes and views (Folder 1 of 3), undated, 29 prints; PH152-155_001-002, PH157-176, and PH197-200 (Box-folder 27/242)
    - Landscapes and views (Folder 2 of 3), undated, 18 prints; PH177-183, PH185, PH187-196 (Box-folder 27/243)
    - Landscapes and views (Folder 3 of 3), undated, 11 prints; PH202-203, PH205-213 (Box-folder 27/244)
    - Events and trips, undated, 44 prints; PH216_0001-216_0006, PH217_0001-0002, PH217_0004-0007, PH217_0009-0012, PH218_0001-0018, PH219, PH220_0001-0002, PH220_0004, PH220_0007-0012 (Box-folder 27/245)
    - Family photos and other images, undated, 2 prints; PH224-225 (Box-folder 27/246)
  - Subseries B: Postcards and drawings
    Includes picture postcards, drawings, etc.
    - Picture postcards, undated, 32 items (Box 28/247)
      commercially-made postcards, both black and white and in color
    - Graphics (miscellaneous) and other materials, undated (Box 28/248)
      - Subfolder A
        - Early depiction of jacket design for Folk Songs of Old New England, drawn by Linscott, undated, 1 item (Box-folder 28/248/A)
      - Subfolder B
        - Pencil tracing from an illustration of a couple, dancing, undated, 1 item (Box-folder 28/248/B)
          See Square Dances and Fiddle Tunes of New England for similar illustrations.
      - Subfolder C
        - Rubbings made on paper, with regular and colored pencils, undated, 3 items (Box-folder 28/248/C)
      - Subfolder D
        - Watercolor image on paper, showing a house in a rural area, undated, 1 item (Box-folder 28/248/D)
      - Subfolder E
        - Envelope and notes, undated, 13 items (Box-folder 28/248/E)
          Water color art work on the envelope, depicting a forest and lake. The scene depicted may be Camp Ossipee, in Wolfeboro, New Hampshire. The envelope has the words “Endowment Fund” painted on it. The miscellaneous notes were formerly in the envelope
      - Subfolder F
        - Pencil drawings of Wolfeboro Neck,, circa 1944 (Box-folder 28/248/F)
      - Subfolder G
        - Pencil drawing by William J. (Jack) Sherrard, November 18, 1965, 1 item (Box-folder 28/248/G)
  - Subseries C: Itemized list of photographs
    The photos listed above were (with a few exceptions) digitized; the list below is a log of the images. The phyiscal item number concords to the digital item ID; e.g., PH001 is the source image for ph001, etc.
    - John Hubbard Linscott as a baby, 1929, 1 print: gelatin silver; afc1942002_ms084_0006
      Originally taped to the dedication page.
    - Eloise Hubbard, with her sisters Helen and Jennie (Jane), 1 print: gelatin silver; afc1942002_ms085_0002
      Originally taped opposite page 1.
    - Fred Pullen, Mrs. Fred Pullen, and Frederick W. Pullen, Jr., 1 print: gelatin silver; afc1942002_ms085_0018
      Originally taped to page 15. See afc1942002_ph102 for a similar image.
    - Frederick W. Pullen, Jr., 1 print: gelatin silver; afc1942002_ms085_0024
      Originally taped to page 19.
    - Serena J. Frye and Mary P. Frye (from left to right), 1 print: gelatin silver; afc1942002_ms085_0052
      Originally taped to page 41. See afc1942002_ph032 for a similar image.
    - Sign for Weed’s Barn Dance, 1 print: gelatin silver; afc1942002_ms086_0009
      Originally taped to page 62. See afc1942002_ph188 for a similar image.
    - Smith Paine, seated, playing fiddle, 1 print: gelatin silver; afc1942002_ms086_0017
      Originally taped to page 68. See afc1942002_ph088 for a similar image.
    - Dennis McClure, standing on sidewalk, 1 print: gelatin silver; afc1942002_ms086_0025
      Originally taped to page 73. See afc1942002_ph077 for a similar image.
    - Dance hall (exterior view), and a person standing by a car, 1 print: gelatin silver; afc1942002_ms086_0037
      Originally taped to page 81. See afc1942002_ph167 for a similar image.
    - Cassius (Cash) Radford, seated, holding a baby, 1 print: gelatin silver; afc1942002_ms086_0044
      Originally taped to page 85. See afc1942002_ph104 for a similar image.
    - Edson H. Cole, seated, holding fiddle and bow, 1 print: gelatin silver; afc1942002_ms086_0063
      Originally taped to page 101. See afc1942002_ph022 for a similar image.
    - Willie (Bill) Woodward, 1 print: gelatin silver; afc1942002_ms086_0076
      Originally taped to page 111. See afc1942002_ph140 for a similar image.
    - Gloucester fisherman statue, 1 print: gelatin silver; afc1942002_ms087_0003
      Originally taped to page 121. See afc1942002_ph186 for a similar image.
    - Charlton Lyman Smith, outdoors, 1 print: gelatin silver; afc1942002_ms087_0009
      Originally taped to page 125. See afc1942002_ph123 for a similar image.
    - Susan A. Hanson’s tombstone, 1 print: gelatin silver; afc1942002_ms088_0024
      Originally taped to page 175. See afc1942002_ph184 for a similar image.
    - Farmington Canal and the towpath, 1 print: gelatin silver; afc1942002_ms088_0047
      Originally taped to page 195. See afc1942002_ph156 for a similar image.
    - Sam Young, Jr.; unidentified man at left is partially obscured, 1 print: gelatin silver; afc1942002_ms088_0074
      Originally taped to page 217. See afc1942002_ph141 for a similar image.
    - The Allen homestead, 1 print: gelatin silver; afc1942002_ms088_0085
      Originally taped to page 225. See afc1942002_ph176 for an alternate view.
    - Lee Johnson and Jennie Hardy Linscott (from left to right), 1 print: gelatin silver; afc1942002_ms088_0098
      Originally taped to page 233. See afc1942002_ph151 for a similar image.
    - Jennie Hardy Linscott, with a dog, in a kitchen, 1 print: gelatin silver; afc1942002_ms088_0131
      Originally taped to page 262.
    - Ma Horn [Frances Horn], 1 print: gelatin silver; afc1942002_ms088_0171
      Originally taped to page 299. See afc1942002_ph048 for a similar image.
    - Will E. Ayer and George Andrew (Stonewall) Jackson, April 18, 1943, 1 negative: 1.75 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph001
      Location: Manchester, New Hampshire. Handwritten note on reverse: April 18, 1943; Will Ayer - fiddler - singer; Geo. Jackson - lumberman; fiddler; legislator.
    - Will E. Ayer and George Andrew (Stonewall) Jackson, April 18, 1943, 1 negative: 1.75 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph002
      Location: Manchester, New Hampshire.
    - Will E. Ayer and Llewellyn S. Powers, undated, 1 print: gelatin silver; 4.5 x 6.5 in.; afc1942002_ph003
      Location: New Hampshire. Poem on the verso by Ayer, in his handwriting.
    - Mrs. Lillian E. Beacham, knitting, November 1945, 1 negative: 3 x 1.75 in.; afc1942002_ph004
      Location: Wolfeboro, New Hampshire. Mother of Gertrude Beacham Hamm.
    - Mrs. Lillian E. Beacham, November 1945, 1 negative: 2.5 x 1.75 in.; afc1942002_ph005
    - Mrs. Lillian E. Beacham, holding her great-granddaughter in her lap, November 1945, 1 negative: 2.5 x 1.75 in.; afc1942002_ph006
    - Mrs. Lillian E. Beacham, holding her great-granddaughter and a cat in her lap, November 1945, 1 negative: 2.75 x 1.75 in.; afc1942002_ph007
    - Mrs. Gertrude Beacham Hamm, seated, in kitchen, 1945, 1 print: gelatin silver; 2.75 x 4.25 in.; afc1942002_ph008
      Location: 81 Bay Street, Wolfeboro, New Hampshire. Daughter of Lillian E. Beacham.
    - Mr. And Mrs. Bill Bonyun, August 1975, 1 color print: dye coupler; 5.75 x 3.5 in.; afc1942002_ph009
      Handwritten note on reverse: "They sang at W. [?] Historical Society 50th - Open House Day; From Wiscasset, Me.; Ballad-Teachers; Aug. 75; The Bonyuns."
    - Harry E. Brigham, circa 1930-1939, 1 photomechanical print: 10 x 6.5 in; afc1942002_ph010
      Location: Marlborough, Massachusetts.
    - L.C. (Pop) Brock, standing outside a house, January-February 1947, 1 negative: 3.5 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph011
      Location: Wolfeboro, New Hampshire.
    - Brother Ricardo Belden, a Shaker, August 22, 1955, 1 color negative: safety; 2.5 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph012
      Location: Lebanon, New York.
    - Brother Ricardo Belden, a Shaker (three-quarter length portrait), August 22, 1955, 1 color negative: safety; 2.5 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph013
    - George (Rocky Mountain George) Brown, holding an object; photographed from inside a car, November 16, 1941, 1 negative: 1.75 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph014
      Location: Tamworth, New Hampshire.